# KUMMARI TIRUPATHI RAO

Palasa



tirupathi9436@gmail.com



9010640342



linkedin.com/in/kummari-tirupathi-rao-290b65161



https://ktr-hub.github.io/

### Summary

Worked as a C# developer for 2.5+ years.

Strong command of the C, C# and C++ programming languages as well as the Unity game engine.

Contributed to a Unity project for a video game that had more than 1 lakh downloads.

I am a team player and am an efficient communicator. I'm currently looking for employment in a game development studio as a game programmer.

### **Experience**



### **RRR The Game Ride Race Rescue**

SK-GAMES

Dec 2022 - Jan 2023 (2 months)

I have contributed to the RRR game project.

RRR-The Game is a third-person Racing Adventure Game, where you can choose to play as Ram or Bheem. Race against time to save the boy who is trapped under the bridge because of a massive fire accident caused by a derailed freight train.

Competencies:

C# Unity for Game Development

ProBuilder and UModeler for Game Modelling/Designing

# **Associate Consultant**

Capgemini

Jan 2022 - Present (1 year 4 months)

- Demonstrated experience and good hands-on programming experience C#.
- Key contributor in the design and implementation of new features.

# Senior Analyst

Capgemini

Sep 2020 - Dec 2021 (1 year 4 months)

### **Machine Learning Intern**

**Hivericks Technologies** 

May 2019 - Jul 2019 (3 months)

- Internship at Hivericks Technologies Private Limited, Chennai.
- Implemented a machine learning model to predict battery discharge rate based on user usage patterns.

#### **Education**

National Institute of Technology Meghalaya

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Electronics and Communications Engineering 2016 - 2020

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

- Photon Unity Networking for Realtime Multiplayer FPS Game Udemy UC-e3210959-e731-4ab0-8912-17d1444a6123
- **Design Patterns for Game Programming** Udemy UC-6856 feb8-c908-42d1-8785-700e2f065bb3
- Unity's Mecanim System & Mixamo for constructing and programming own third-person game character Udemy

  UC-fa7e805e-984d-409c-8407-4085f0439c5e
- Associate Innvator Capgemini
- Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals Microsoft 1395-5733
- AWS Game Day Amazon Web Services (AWS)

#### **Skills**

C# in .NET • Unity • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Design Patterns • Data Structures • Algorithms • Microsoft Azure • Agile Methodologies • Adobe Photoshop • After Effects

### **Honors & Awards**

Young Emerging Professional - Capgemini Dec 2022